Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Newsprint Comic Strips RL.11749
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Edwin and Terry Murray collection of newsprint comic strips
1920s-1980s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Murray, Edwin, and Terry Murray (collectors)
RL.11749
64 Linear Feet
Collection consists of Edwin and Terry Murray's collection of clipped comic strips from newspapers, including Blondie, B.C., Gasoline Alley, Gordo, Buz Sawyer, Apartment 3-G, Bugs Bunny, Archie, Mary Worth, Moon Mullins, Out Our Way, Judge Parker, Steve Canyon, Kerry Drake, Campus Clatter, Chief Wahoo, Priscilla's Pop, Green Beret, Hi and Lois, Boner's Ark, Dennis the Menace, The Jackson Twins, RIP Kirby, Wizard of Id, Smilin' Jack, Beetle Bailey, Popeye, and many others; as well as assorted full comics sections (also known as funnies) from American newspapers such as The Washington Post, the New Orleans Times-Picayune, the Overseas Weekly, the Detroit Free Press, The Chicago Defender, Asbury Park Sunday Press, The Durham Sun, The Durham Morning Herald, The Greenville News, and The News and Observer (Raleigh, N.C.). The bulk of the comic strips date from the 1950s through 1970s.
Arrangement
Collection is sorted into series: Clipped Strips and Newspaper Comics Sections.
Biographical / Historical
Edwin L. and Terry A. Murray, brothers residing in Durham, North Carolina, have been collectors of comic books and other pulp culture for fifty years.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Newsprint Comic Strips were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2019.
Related Materials
The Rubenstein Library also holds the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Fanzines; the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Pulp Culture; and the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-playing Games. Search "Edwin and Terry Murray" as an author in the catalog to find additional comic books, cataloged separately.
Collection Overview
Collection consists of Edwin and Terry Murray's collection of clipped comic strips from newspapers, including Blondie, B.C., Gasoline Alley, Gordo, Buz Sawyer, Apartment 3-G, Bugs Bunny, Archie, Mary Worth, Moon Mullins, Out Our Way, Judge Parker, Steve Canyon, Kerry Drake, Campus Clatter, Chief Wahoo, Priscilla's Pop, Green Beret, Hi and Lois, Boner's Ark, Dennis the Menace, The Jackson Twins, RIP Kirby, Wizard of Id, Smilin' Jack, Beetle Bailey, Popeye, and many others; as well as assorted full comics sections (also known as funnies) from American newspapers such as The Washington Post, the New Orleans Times-Picayune, the Overseas Weekly, the Detroit Free Press, The Chicago Defender, Asbury Park Sunday Press, The Durham Sun, The Durham Morning Herald, The Greenville News, and The News and Observer (Raleigh, N.C.). The bulk of the comic strips date from the 1950s through 1970s.
Murray, Edwin L. Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Pulp Culture; United States -- Newspapers; Newspaper reading -- Research; Comic strip characters; Newspapers -- Sections, columns, etc. -- Comics; Comic books, strips, etc.; Racism in cartoons
- Clipped newsprint comic strips, 1920s-1980s; 1
  Scope and Contents
  Series consists of clipped newspaper and newsprint comic strips collected by the Murrays and bundled by title and date. Items have been filed as best as possible in loose chronological order, arranged alphabetically by title of the comic strip.
  - Alley Oop, 1943 (Box 91)
  - Alley Oop, 1948 (Box 52)
  - Alley Oop, 1948 (Box 52)
  - Alley Oop, 1956, 1963-1964 (Box 52)
  - Alley Oop, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 52)
  - Alley Oop, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 52)
  - Alley Oop, 1967; scattered (Box 52)
  - Alley Oop, 1967 (Box 92)
  - Alley Oop, 1970; scattered (Box 52)
  - Alley Oop, 1971; scattered (Box 52)
  - Alley Oop, 1972 Jan-May 20 (Box 52)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1971; Scattered (Box 49)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1961 May-Dec (Box 28)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1961-1964; Scattered (Box 49)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1962 Jan-Jun (Box 28)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 28)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1963 Apr-Jul (Box 28)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1963 Jul-Dec (Box 28)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1964-1968; Scattered (Box 28)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1967 (Box 94)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1967-1968 (Box 94)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1969 Jan-Jun (Box 28)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1971 Jul-Dec (Box 28)
  - Apartment 3-G, 1971 (Box 94)
  - Archie, 1949 Jan-Jun (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1949 Jul-Dec (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1950 Jan-Jun (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1950 Jul-Dec (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1951 Jan-Jun (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1951 Jul-Dec (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1952 Jan-Jun (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1952 Jul-Dec (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1953 Jan-Jun (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1953 Jul-Dec (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1954 Jan-Jun; mixed (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1954 Jul-Dec (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1958 Incomplete; incomplete (Box 36)
  - Archie, 1959 Jan-Jun (Box 36)
  - Archie, 1959 Jul-Dec (Box 36)
  - Archie, 1960; Scattered (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1961 (Box 36)
  - Archie, 1961; Scattered (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1962; Scattered (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1964 Jan-Jun (Box 49)
  - Archie, 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 49)
  - Archie, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 36)
  - Archie, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 36)
  - Archie, 1966 Jan-Aug 13 (Box 36)
  - Archie, 1966; Scattered (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1966 Sep 10-Dec (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1967 Jan-Oct (Box 49)
  - Archie, 1969 Feb-Nov (Box 49)
  - Archie, 1970 Apr-Oct 24 (Box 36)
  - Archie, 1970 Oct 26-Dec (Box 37)
  - Archie, 1972 (Box 37)
  - B.C., 1958 Feb 17-Dec (Box 41)
  - B.C., 1959 (Box 41)
  - B.C., 1960 (Box 41)
  - B.C., 1961 (Box 41)
  - B.C., 1962 Jan-Jun (Box 52)
  - B.C., 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 52)
  - B.C., 1963 Jan-Jun (Box 52)
  - B.C., 1963 Jul-Dec (Box 52)
  - Barney Google and Snuffy Smith, 1952 (Box 46)
  - Barney Google and Snuffy Smith, 1953 Jan-Jun (Box 46)
  - Barney Google and Snuffy Smith, 1953 Jul-Dec (Box 46)
  - Barney Google and Snuffy Smith, 1954 Jan-Jun (Box 46)
  - Barney Google and Snuffy Smith, 1954 Jul-Nov (Box 46)
  - Batman, 1966 (Box 42)
  - Batman, 1967 (Box 42)
  - Batman, 1968 (Box 42)
  - Batman and Robin, 1945 (Box 42)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1950 Oct-Dec (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1952 Jan-Jun (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1952 Jul-Dec (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1953 Jan-Jun (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1953 Jul-Dec (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1954 Jan-Jun (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1954 Jul-Dec (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1955 (Box 59)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1955 (Box 59)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1956 (Box 59)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1956 (Box 59)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1957 (Box 59)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1957 (Box 59)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1959 Jul-Dec (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1959 Mar-Jun (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1961 May-Dec (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1962 (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1963 Jan-Jun (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1963 Jul-Dec (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1964 Jan-Jun (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1966 Jan-May (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1966 Jun-Aug (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1967 (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1969 Jan-Jun (Box 29)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1969 Jul-Oct (Box 33)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1971 (Box 33)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1972 (Box 59)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1972 (Box 59)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1973 (Box 59)
  - Beetle Bailey, 1973 (Box 59)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1952 (Box 59)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1952 (Box 79)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1953 (Box 79)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1953 (Box 79)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1954 (Box 79)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1954 (Box 79)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1960-1963 (Box 91)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1961 Jan-Dec (Box 100)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1962 Mar-Dec (Box 100)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1963 Jan-Oct (Box 100)
  - Big Ben Bolt, 1970 (Box 100)
  - Blondie, 1938 Jan-Jun (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1939 Jul-Dec (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1943 Feb-Jun (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1943 Jul-Dec (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1944 Aug-Dec (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1944 Jan-Jun (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1945 Jan-Jun (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1945 Jul-Nov (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1946 Feb-May (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1946 Jul-Dec (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1947 (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1948 (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1950 (Box 42)
  - Blondie, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1955 (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1956 Jan-Jun (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1956 Jul-Dec (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1957 Jan-Jun (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1957 Jul-Sep (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1958 (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1960 (Box 23)
  - Blondie, 1961 (Box 23)
  - Boner's Ark, 1968 (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1969 Feb-Jun (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1969 Jul-Dec (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1970 Jan-Jun (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1970 Jul-Dec (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1971 Jan-Jun (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1971 Jul-Dec (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1972 Jan-Jun (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1972 Jul-Dec (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1973 Jan-Jun (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1973 Jul-Dec (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1974 Jan-Jun (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1974 Jul-Dec (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1975 Jan-Jun (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1975 Jul-Dec (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1976 Jan-Jun (Box 45)
  - Boner's Ark, 1976 Jul-Dec (Box 45)
  - Boots and Her Buddies, 1932; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Broom Hilda, 1970 (Box 57)
  - Bucky's Christmas Caper, 1967 (Box 26)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1948 (Box 31)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1949 Jan-Jun (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1949 Jul-Dec (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1950 Jan-Jun (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1950 Jul-Dec (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1951 Jan-Jun (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1951-1956 (Box 92)
    scattered
  - Bugs Bunny, 1951 Jul-Dec (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1952 Jan-Jun (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1952 Jul-Dec (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1953 Jan-Jun (Box 31)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1953 Jul-Dec (Box 31)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1970 Jan-Jun (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1970 Jul-Dec (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1971 Jan-Jun (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1971 Jul-Dec (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1972 Jan-Jun (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1972 Jul-Dec (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1973 Jan-Jun (Box 58)
  - Bugs Bunny, 1973 Jul-Dec (Box 58)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1959 Aug-Dec (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1960 Jan-Jun (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1960 Jul-Dec (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1961 Jan-Jun (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1961 Jul-Dec (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1962 Jan-Jun (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1963-1964 (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1965 Jan 21-Jun (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1966 Jan-Jul 16 (Box 52)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1971 (Box 38)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1972 (Box 38)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1973 (Box 38)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1976 (Box 38)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1977 (Box 38)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1978 (Box 38)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1979-1980 (Box 38)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1980-1981 (Box 38)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1982; unsorted (Box 38)
  - Buz Sawyer, 1987-1988; unsorted (Box 38)
  - Calvin and Hobbes, 1987 (Box 99)
  - Campus Clatter, 1969 Jul-Dec (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1970 Jan-Jun (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1970 Jul-Dec (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1971 Jan-Jun (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1971 Jul-Dec (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1972 Jan-Jun (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1972 Jul-Dec (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1973 Jan-Jun (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1973 Jul-Dec (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1974 Jan-Jun (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1974 Jul-Dec (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1975 Jan-Jun (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1975 Jul-Dec (Box 40)
  - Campus Clatter, 1976 Jan-Sep (Box 40)
  - Capt. Kate, 1967 May-Dec (Box 40)
  - Capt. Kate, 1968 Aug-Dec (Box 40)
  - Capt. Kate, 1968 Feb-Jul (Box 40)
  - Captain Easy, 1955 (Box 100)
  - Captain Easy, 1956-1957 (Box 100)
  - Captain Easy, 1958-1959 (Box 100)
  - Captain Easy, 1960-1962 (Box 100)
  - Captain Easy, 1963 Jun-Oct (Box 100)
  - Captain Easy, 1964 Feb-Sep (Box 100)
  - Captain Easy, 1970 (Box 59)
  - Captain Easy, 1971 (Box 59)
  - Captain Easy, 1972 (Box 59)
  - Captain Easy, 1972 (Box 59)
  - Chief Wahoo, 1943 Feb-Jun (Box 43)
  - Chief Wahoo, 1943 Jul-Dec (Box 43)
  - Chief Wahoo, 1945 Jan-Jun (Box 43)
  - Chief Wahoo, 1945 Jul-Nov (Box 43)
  - Chief Wahoo, 1946 Jan-Jun (Box 43)
  - Chief Wahoo, 1946 Jul-Dec (Box 43)
  - Chief Wahoo, 1947 Jan-Jun (Box 43)
  - Chief Wahoo, 1947 Jul-Dec (Box 43)
  - Cranberry Boggs, 1946 (Box 80)
  - Cranberry Boggs, 1946 (Box 80)
  - Dan Flagg, 1963 Jul-Dec (Box 50)
  - Dan Flagg, 1964 Jan-Jun (Box 50)
  - Dan Flagg, 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 50)
  - Dan Flagg, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 50)
  - Dan Flagg, 1965 Jul-Sep 11 (Box 50)
  - Daniel Boone, 1955 (Box 26)
  - Dateline Danger, 1968 (Box 42)
  - Dateline Danger, 1968-1969 (Box 92)
  - Dateline Danger, 1969 (Box 92)
  - Dateline Danger, 1969 (Box 42)
  - Dateline Danger, 1969 (Box 42)
  - Dateline Danger, 1969-1970 (Box 92)
  - Dateline Danger, 1970 (Box 42)
  - Dateline Danger, 1970-1971 (Box 92)
  - Dateline Danger, 1971 (Box 42)
  - Dateline Danger, 1971 (Box 42)
  - Davy Crockett, 1955 (Box 75)
  - Davy Crockett, 1956 (Box 75)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1952 (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1953 (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1953 (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1954 (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1954 (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1955 Jan-Jun (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1955 Jul-Dec (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1956 Jan-Jun (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1956 Jul-Dec (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1957 Jan-Jun (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1957 Jul-Dec (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1958 Jan-Jun (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1958 Jul-Dec (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1959 Jan-Jun (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1959 Jul-Dec (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1960 Jan-Jun (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1960 Jul-Dec (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1961 Jan-Jun (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1961 Jul-Dec (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1962 Jan-Jun (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1963 Jan-Jun (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1963 Jul-Dec (Box 53)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1964 Jan-Jun (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1966 Jan-Jun (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1966 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1967 Jan-Jun (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1967 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1968 Feb-Jun (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1968 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1969 Jan-Jun (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1969 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1970 Jan-Jun (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1970 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1978 Feb-Dec (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1979 Jan-Jun (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1979 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1980 Jan-Jun (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1980 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Dennis the Menace, 1981 Jan-Mar (Box 54)
  - Dick Tracy, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 37)
  - Dick Tracy, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 37)
  - Dixie Dugan, 1957; Scattered (Box 28)
  - Dixie Dugan /Joe Palooka / Blondie, 1954 (Box 48)
  - Dixie Dugan/Blondie, 1950s (Box 28)
  - Dotty Dripple, 1954 (Box 42)
  - Draftie, 1943 (Box 26)
  - Dragnet, 1952 (Box 57)
  - Dragnet, 1953 (Box 57)
  - Flash Gordon, 1965 (Box 60)
  - Flash Gordon, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Flash Gordon, 1967 (Box 60)
  - The Flintstones, 1961 (Box 49)
  - The Flintstones, 1961 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1962 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1963 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1963 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1964 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1964 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1965 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1965 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1966 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1966 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1967 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1967 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1968 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1968 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1969 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1969 (Box 57)
  - The Flintstones, 1970 (Box 57)
  - Freckles, 1925, 1934 (Box 49)
  - Freckles, 1944 (Box 75)
  - Freckles, 1949 Jul-Dec (Box 75)
  - Freckles, 1952 (Box 75)
  - Freckles, 1953 (Box 75)
  - Freckles, 1954 (Box 75)
  - Freckles, 1955 (Box 75)
  - Freckles, 1956-1957 (Box 36)
  - Freckles, 1956-1957 (Box 36)
  - Freckles, 1956-1957 (Box 36)
  - Freckles, 1956-1957 (Box 36)
  - Freckles, 1957 (Box 75)
  - Freckles, 1958 (Box 75)
  - Freckles, 1958 (Box 75)
  - Freckles, 1959 (Box 75)
  - Freckles, 1959 (Box 76)
  - Freckles, 1960 (Box 76)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1940 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1946 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1947 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1947 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1948 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1948 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1949 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1949 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1950 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1950 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1951 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1951 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1952 Jan-Jun (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1952 Jul-Dec (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1953 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1953 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1954 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1954 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1955 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1955 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1957 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1957 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1958 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1958 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1959 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1959 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1960 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1960 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1961 Jan-Jun (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1961 Jul-Dec (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1962 Jan-Jun (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1963 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1963 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1964 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1964 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1965 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1965 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1966 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1966 (Box 34)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1967 (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1967 (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1968 (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1968 (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1968 (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1968 (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1969 (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1969 (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Alley, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Alley / Freddy, 1956 (Box 49)
  - Gil Thorp, 1980s; 4 folders (Box 59)
  - Gordo, 1943-1949 (Box 98)
    Scattered
  - Gordo, 1948; Scattered (Box 30)
  - Gordo, 1948 (Box 94)
  - Gordo, 1954; Scattered (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1948 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1948 (Box 99)
  - Gordo, 1949-1958; 19 folders (Box 98)
  - Gordo, 1949 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1949 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1950 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1950 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1951 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1951 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1952 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1952 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1953 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1953 (Box 51)
  - Gordo, 1959-1963; 9 folders (Box 99)
  - Gordo, 1961; Scattered (Box 30)
  - Gordo, 1963; Scattered (Box 30)
  - Gordo, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 30)
  - Gordo, 1965; Scattered (Box 30)
  - Gordo, 1966 Jan-Jun (Box 30)
  - Gordo, 1967; Scattered (Box 30)
  - Half Hitch, 1970 (Box 50)
  - Half Hitch, 1970 (Box 50)
  - Half Hitch, 1971; scattered (Box 50)
  - Hi and Lois, 1955; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1955 (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1956; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1956 (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1957; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1957 (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1958; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1959; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1959 (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1960; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1960 (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1961; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1961 (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1962 Jan-Jun (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1963 Jan-Jun (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1963 Jul-Dec (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1964 Jan-Jun (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 47)
  - Hi and Lois, 1966 Jan-Sep (Box 47)
  - Hopalong Cassidy, 1950 Jan-Jun (Box 48)
  - Hopalong Cassidy, 1950 Jul-Dec (Box 48)
  - Hopalong Cassidy, 1951 (Box 48)
  - Hopalong Cassidy, 1951 Jan-Jun (Box 28)
  - Hopalong Cassidy, 1951 Jul-Dec (Box 28)
  - Hopalong Cassidy, 1952 Jan-Jun (Box 28)
  - Hopalong Cassidy, 1952 Jul-Dec (Box 28)
  - Hopalong Cassidy, 1954 Jan-Jun (Box 28)
  - Hopalong Cassidy, 1954 Jul-Dec (Box 28)
  - Hunter Keene, 1946 (Box 26)
  - The Jackson Twins, 1950s; 5 folders (Box 74)
  - The Jackson Twins, 1960s; 7 folders (Box 74)
  - James Bond, 1965 (Box 81)
  - Joe Palooka, Undated (Box 43)
  - Joe Palooka, Undated (Box 43)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1960 (Box 43)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1961 (Box 43)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1961 (Box 43)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1964 (Box 43)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1965 (Box 43)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1966 (Box 43)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1966 (Box 43)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1966-1970 (Box 92)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1970-1971 (Box 92)
  - Johnny Hazard, 1971-1972 (Box 92)
  - Judd Saxon, 1957; 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Judd Saxon, 1958; 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Judd Saxon, 1959; 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Judd Saxon, 1960; 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Judd Saxon, 1960 (Box 46)
  - Judd Saxon, 1961 (Box 46)
  - Judge Parker, 1950s-1960s; undated (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1950s-1960s; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1954-1955 (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1956 (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1958 Jan-Jun (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1958 Jul-Dec (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1959 Jan-Jun (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1959 Jul-Dec (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1960 Jan-Jun (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1960 Jul-Dec (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1961 Jan-Jun (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1961 Jul-Dec (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1962 Jan-Jun (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1963 Jan-Jun (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1963 Jul-Dec (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1964 Jan-Jun (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1966 Jan-Jun (Box 27)
  - Judge Parker, 1966-1967 Jul-Jan (Box 27)
  - Juliet Jones, 1953 Jul-Dec (Box 46)
  - Juliet Jones, 1953 Mar-Jun (Box 46)
  - Juliet Jones, 1954 Jan-Jun (Box 46)
  - Juliet Jones, 1954 Jul-Dec (Box 46)
  - Juliet Jones, 1955 Jan-Jun (Box 46)
  - Juliet Jones, 1955 Jul-Aug (Box 46)
  - Kerry Drake, 1948-1950 (Box 92)
  - Kerry Drake, 1949 Jan-Jun (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1949 Jul-Dec (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1949 Sep 12-Dec (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1950 Jan-Jun (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1950 Jul-Dec 30 (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1951 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1951 Jul-Dec (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1952 Jan-Jun (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1952 Jul-Dec (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1953 Jan-Jun (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1953 Jul-Dec (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1954 Jan-Jun (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1954 Jul-Dec (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1955 Jan-Jun (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1955 Jul-Dec (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1956 Jan-Jun (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1956 Jul-Dec (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1957 Jan-Jun (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1957 Jul-Dec (Box 39)
  - Kerry Drake, 1958 Jan-Jun (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1958 Jul-Dec (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1959 Jan-Jun (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1959 Jul-Dec (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1960 Jan-Jun (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1960 Jul-Dec (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1961 Jan-Jun (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1961 Jul-Dec (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1962 Jan-Jun (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1963 Jan-Jun (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1963 Jul-Dec (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1964-1966 (Box 100)
  - Kerry Drake, 1965 Jan-Jun; incomplete (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, 1966 Jan-May (Box 41)
  - Kerry Drake, Steve Roper, and Steve Canyon, 1955-1956 (Box 103)
  - Kerry Drake, Steve Roper, and Steve Canyon, 1957-1958 (Box 103)